A Guide to the Records of the Policy Office: Regulations of Governor Lawrence Douglas Wilder, 1990-1994
Library of Virginia
- DPOR--Real Estate Board--Public Participation Guidelines--VR 585-01-01, 1993. (Box 22, Folder 7)
- DPOR--Virginia Asbestos Licensing Regulations--VR 190-05-02, 1993-1994. (Box 22, Folder 8)
- DYFS--Emergency Regulations--Minimum Standards for the Detention of Juveniles in Jails and Lockups, 1993. (Box 22, Folder 9)
- Economic Development--Emergency Regulations--Public Participation Guidelines (1 of 2), 1993. (Box 22, Folder 10)
- Economic Development--Emergency Regulations--Public Participation Guidelines (2 of 2), 1993. (Box 22, Folder 11)
- Economic Development--Gypsy Moth Quarantine--VR 115-04-02, 1992. (Box 22, Folder 12)
- Economic Development--Housing and Community Development--Local Housing Rehabilitation Program--VR 394-01-102, 1991. (Box 22, Folder 13)
- Economic Development--Housing and Community Development--Multi-family Loan Program--VR 394-01-103, 1991. (Box 22, Folder 14)
- Economic Development--Meat and Poultry Inspection--VR 115-02-19, 1992. (Box 22, Folder 15)
- Economic Development--Prevention, Control, and Eradication of Bucellosis--VR 115-02-03, 1992. (Box 22, Folder 16)
- Economic Development--Weights and Measures Law--VR 115-04-04, 1992. (Box 23, Folder 1)
- Education--Accrediting Public Schools--VR 270-01-0012, 1992. (Box 23, Folder 2)
- Education--Approved Programs for Institutions of Higher Learning--VR 270-01-0052.1, 1992. (Box 23, Folder 3)
- Education--Educational Programs for Gifted Students--VR 270-01-0002, 1992-1993. (Box 23, Folder 4)
- Education--Emergency Regulations--Pilot Programs for Alternative Education Program--VR 270-01-0058, 1993. (Box 23, Folder 5)
- Education--Emergency Regulations--Proprietary Career Schools Fees and Assessments--VR 270-01-0056, 1992-1993. (Box 23, Folder 6)
- Education--Emergency Regulations--Public Participation Guidelines, 1993. (Box 23, Folder 7)
- Education--Employment of Professional Personnel--VR 270-01-0042.1, 1993-1994. (Box 23, Folder 8)
- Education--Licensure for School Personnel--VR 270-01-0000.1 (1 of 2), 1992-1993. (Box 23, Folder 9)
- Education--Licensure for School Personnel--VR 270-01-0000.1 (2 of 2), 1992-1993. (Box 23, Folder 10)
- Education--Literary Fund Loan Applications--VR 270-01-0009, 1993. (Box 24, Folder 1)
- Education--Operation of Proprietary Schools and Issuing of Agent Permits--VR 270-01-0034, 1993. (Box 24, Folder 2)
- Education--Reporting Acts of Violence and Substance Abuse in Schools-VR 270-01-0052, 1991-1992. (Box 24, Folder 3)
- Education--Special Education Programs for Children with Disabilities--VR 270-02-0007 (1 of 2), 1993. (Box 24, Folder 4)
- Education--Special Education Programs for Children with Disabilities--VR 270-02-0007 (2 of 2), 1993. (Box 24, Folder 5)
- Education--Special Education Program Standards--VR 270-01-0057, 1993. (Box 24, Folder 6)
- Environment--Emergency Regulations--Environmental Impact Assessment for Permit to Drill Oil or Gas Well--VR 305-01-001, 1991. (Box 24, Folder 7)
- Environment--Preparation of Environmental Impact Assessment for Oil and Gas Well Drilling in Tidewater, 1991. (Box 24, Folder 8)
- Environment--Preparation of Environmental Impact Assessment for Oil and Gas Well Drilling in Tidewater--VR 305-02-01, 1991-1992. (Box 24, Folder 9)
- Environment--Public Participation Guidelines--VR 305-01-001, 1991. (Box 24, Folder 10)
- Environment--Public Participation Guidelines--VR 305-01-001, 1992-1993. (Box 24, Folder 11)
- Environment Quality--Regulated Medical Waste Management--VR 672-40-01:1, 1993. (Box 24, Folder 12)
- Gas and Oil Board--Conservation of Gas and Oil Resources and Protect Correlative Rights of Resource Owners--VR 480-05-22.1, 1991. (Box 25, Folder 1)
- General Services--Approval of Field Tests for the Detection of Drugs, 1991-1992. (Box 25, Folder 2)
- General Services--Certification of Laboratories Analyzing Drinking Water--VR 330-02-06:1, 1993. (Box 25, Folder 3)
- General Services--Final Clearance Inspections for Asbestos Projects--VR 330-03-02, 1992-1993. (Box 25, Folder 4)
- General Services--Prenatal Serological Tests for Syphilis, 1991-1992. (Box 25, Folder 5)
- General Services--Standards for Devices Used to Measure Light Transmittance through Vehicle Windshields--VR 330-04-04, 1993. (Box 25, Folder 6)
- Health--Alternative Discharging Sewage Treatment for Individual, Single Family Dwellings--VR 355-34-400, 1992. (Box 25, Folder 7)
- Health--Board of Audiology and Speech Pathology--VR 155-01-2, 1991. (Box 25, Folder 8)
- Health--Board of Dentistry--VR 255-01-1, 1991. (Box 25, Folder 9)
- Health--Board of Nursing--Home Administrators Regulations--VR 500-01-2.1, 1991. (Box 25, Folder 10)
- Health--Board of Nursing Regulations--VR 495-01-1, 1991. (Box 25, Folder 11)
- Health--Conduct of Human Research--VR 335-40-600, 1992-1993. (Box 25, Folder 12)
- Health--Disease Reporting and Control--VR 355-18-100.5, 1993. (Box 26, Folder 1)
- Health--Eligibility Standards and Charges for Medical Care Services--VR 355-39-01, 1992. (Box 26, Folder 2)
- Health--Eligibility Standards and Charges for Medical Care Services-VR 355-39-100, 1993. (Box 26, Folder 3)
- Health--Emergency Medical Services Do Not Resuscitate Program, 1992. (Box 26, Folder 4)
- Health--Emergency Medical Services Do Not Resuscitate Program, 1992. (Box 26, Folder 5)
- Health--Emergency Regulations--Alternative Discharging Sewage Treatment System for Individual Singe Family Dwellings, 1992. (Box 26, Folder 6)
- Health--Emergency Regulations--EMS Do Not Resuscitate Program--VR 355-32-500.E, 1993. (Box 26, Folder 7)
- Health--Emergency Regulations--Immunization of School Children, 1992. (Box 26, Folder 8)
- Health--Emergency Regulations--Public Participation Guidelines (1 of 2), 1993. (Box 26, Folder 9)
- Health--Emergency Regulations--Public Participation Guidelines (2 of 2), 1993. (Box 26, Folder 10)
- Health--Emergency Regulations--Virginia Medical Care Facilities Certificate of Public Need Program, 1991. (Box 27, Folder 1)
- Health--Emergency Regulations--Virginia Medical Care Facilities Certificate of Pubic Need Program, 1992. (Box 27, Folder 2)
- Health--Emergency Regulations--Virginia Medical Scholarship Program--VR 355-40-400.E, 1992. (Box 27, Folder 3)
- Health--Emergency Regulations--Virginia Nurse Practitioner/Nurse Midwife Scholarship--VR 355-40-700.E, 1993. (Box 27, Folder 4)
- Health--Emergency Regulations--Water Works Operation Fee-VR 355-18-014,. (Box 27, Folder 5)
- Health--Emergency Regulations--Water Works Regulations, 1992. (Box 27, Folder 6)
- Health--Environmental Health, Laboratory, and Medical Care Services--VR 355-39-200, 1992-1993. (Box 27, Folder 7)
- Health--Identification of Medically Underserved Areas--VR 355-4005, 1991. (Box 27, Folder 8)
- Health--Immunization of School Children-VR 355-28-300, 1991-1992. (Box 27, Folder 9)
- Health--Licensure of Hospitals--VR 355-33-500, 1991. (Box 27, Folder 10)
- Health--Medical Care Facilities--VR 355-30-000.6, 1992. (Box 28, Folder 1)
- Health--Newborn Screening and Treatment Program--VR 355-11-200, 1992-1993. (Box 28, Folder 2)
- Health--Private Well Regulations--VR 355-34-100, 1992. (Box 28, Folder 3)
- Health--Public Participation Guidelines--VR 355-01-100.1, 1993. (Box 28, Folder 4)
- Health--Rules and Regulations for the Licensure of Hospitals (1 of 2), 1993. (Box 28, Folder 5)
- Health--Rules and Regulations for the Licensure of Hospitals (1 of 2), 1993. (Box 28, Folder 6)
- Health--Virginia Medical Care Facilities--Certificate of Public Need--VR 355-30-000.8E, 1993. (Box 28, Folder 7)
- Health--Virginia Medical Care Facilities--Certificate of Public Need--VR 355-30-000.7, 1993. (Box 29, Folder 1)
- Health--Virginia Medical Care Facilities--Certificate of Public Need--VR 355-30-000.7 (1 of 3), 1993. (Box 29, Folder 2)
- Health--Virginia Medical Care Facilities--Certificate of Public Need--VR 355-30-000.7 (2 of 3), 1993. (Box 29, Folder 3)
- Health--Virginia Medical Care Facilities--Certificate of Public Need--VR 355-30-000.7 (3 of 3), 1993. (Box 29, Folder 4)
- Health--Virginia State Medical Facilities Plan--VR 355-30-100-113, 1993. (Box 29, Folder 5)
- Health--Virginia Medical Scholarship Program--VR 355-4004, 1991. (Box 29, Folder 6)
- Health--Virginia Medical Scholarship Program--VR 355-40-400:1, 1993. (Box 30, Folder 1)
- Health--Waterworks Operation Fee--VR 355-18-014, 1992-1993. (Box 30, Folder 2)
- Health--Waterworks--Total Coliform and Surface Water Treatment (1 of 3), 1992-1993. (Box 30, Folder 3)
- Health--Waterworks--Total Coliform and Surface Water Treatment (2 of 3), 1992-1993. (Box 30, Folder 4)
- Health--Waterworks--Total Coliform and Surface Water Treatment (3 of 3), 1992-1993. (Box 30, Folder 5)
- Health Services--Cost Review Council--Measure Efficiency and Productivity of Health Care Institutions--VR 370-01-002, 1993. (Box 30, Folder 6)
- Health Services--Cost Review Council--Methodology to Measure the Efficiency and Productivity of Health Care Institutions--VR 370-01-001-VR 370-01-02, 1992-1993. (Box 30, Folder 7)
- Health Services--Cost Review Council--Patient Level Data Base System--VR 370-01-003, 1993. (Box 31, Folder 1)
- Health Services--Cost Review Council--Public Participation Guidelines--VR 370-01-000:1, 1993. (Box 31, Folder 2)
- Health Services--Cost Review Council--Rules and Regulations of Council--VR 370-01-001, 1993. (Box 31, Folder 3)
- Health Services--Cost Review Council--Rules and Regulations of Council--VR 370-01-001, 1993. (Box 31, Folder 4)
- Health Services--Cost Review Council--VR 370-01-001, 1993. (Box 31, Folder 5)
- Higher Education--Emergency Regulations--Public Participation Guidelines, 1993. (Box 31, Folder 6)
- Higher Education--Virginia Work Study Program--VR 380-03-02:1, 1993. (Box 31, Folder 7)
- Historic Resources--Criteria and Procedures for Federal Nominations--VR 392-01-02.1, 1993. (Box 31, Folder 8)
- Historic Resources--Criteria and Procedures for Landmark Designations--VR 390-01-03.1, 1993. (Box 31, Folder 9)
- Historic Resources--Emergency Regulations--Evaluation Criteria and Procedures for Designations--VR 390-01-03, 1992. (Box 31, Folder 10)
- Historic Resources--Emergency Regulations--Evaluation Criteria and Procedures for Designations by Board of Historic Resources, 1992. (Box 31, Folder 11)
- Historic Resources--Emergency Regulations--Evaluation Criteria and Procedures for Designations by Board of Historic Resources, 1993. (Box 31, Folder 12)
- Historic Resources--Evaluation Criteria and Procedures for Nominations of Property to the National Park Service for Inclusion in the Register of Historic Places, 1993. (Box 31, Folder 13)
- Historic Resources--Public Participation Guidelines, 1992. (Box 31, Folder 14)
- Housing--Building Maintenance Code--VR 394-01-22, 1993. (Box 31, Folder 15)
- Housing--Certification Standards for Buildings and Amusement Device Inspectors, Blasters, and Trade men, 1992. (Box 31, Folder 16)
- Housing--Congregate Housing Program--VR 394-01-104, 1991. (Box 31, Folder 17)
- Housing--Industrialized Building and Manufactured Home Safety--VR 394-01-31, 1993. (Box 32, Folder 1)
- Housing--Manufactured Housing Licensing and Transaction Recovery Fund--VR 449-01-02, 1993. (Box 32, Folder 2)
- Housing--Public Participation Guidelines--VR 394-01-1, 1993. (Box 32, Folder 3)
- Housing--Public Participation Guidelines--VR 449-01-01, 1993. (Box 32, Folder 4)
- Housing--SHARE--Expansion of Loan Program--VR 394-01-105, 1991. (Box 32, Folder 5)
- Housing--Statewide Fire Prevention Code--VR 394-01-06, 1990-1991. (Box 32, Folder 6)
- Housing--Statewide Fire Prevention Code--VR 394-01-06, 1990-1992. (Box 32, Folder 7)
- Housing--Statewide Fire Prevention Code--VR 394-01-06, 1993. (Box 32, Folder 8)
- Housing--Uniform Statewide Building Code, Vol. 1--New Construction--VR 394-01-21, 1990-1992. (Box 32, Folder 9)
- Housing--Uniform Statewide Building Code, Vol. I--New Construction Code--VR 394-01-21, 1991-1993. (Box 32, Folder 10)
- Housing--Uniform Statewide Building Code, Vol. II--Building Maintenance Code--VR 394-01-22, 1990-1993. (Box 32, Folder 11)
- Housing--Uniform Statewide Building Code--VR 394-01-21, 1993. (Box 32, Folder 12)
- Housing--Virginia Amusement Devise--VR 394-01-04,. (Box 33, Folder 1)
- Housing--Virginia Amusement Devise--VR 394-01-04, 1992-1993. (Box 33, Folder 2)
- Housing--Virginia Amusement Devise--VR 394-01-04, 1993. (Box 33, Folder 3)
- Housing--Virginia Certification Standards--VR 394-01-2, 1993. (Box 33, Folder 4)
- Housing--Virginia Manufactured Housing Board--Emergency Regulations--Public Participation Guidelines--VR 394-01-32, 1993. (Box 33, Folder 5)
- Housing--Virginia Private Activity Bond--VR 394-01-200, 1993. (Box 33, Folder 6)
- Labor and Industry--Apprenticeship Programs--VR 425-01-26, 1993. (Box 33, Folder 7)
- Labor and Industry--Apprenticeship Program--De registration Programs--VR 447-02-1, 1992. (Box 33, Folder 8)
- Labor and Industry--Emergency Regulations--Employment of Minors on Farms, in Gardens, and in Orchards, 1991. (Box 33, Folder 9)
- Labor and Industry--Emergency Regulations--Employment of Minors on Farms, in Gardens, and in Orchards, 1993. (Box 33, Folder 10)
- Labor and Industry--Emergency Regulations--Virginia Occupational Safety and Health Administration Regulations Manual, 1993. (Box 33, Folder 11)
- Labor and Industry--Employment of Minors on Farms, in Gardens, and in Orchards, 1991-1992. (Box 33, Folder 12)
- Library [Virginia State Library and Archive]--VR 440-01-127.2, VR 440-01-137.1, VR 440-01-137.4-440-01-137.8, 1990-1991. (Box 34, Folder 1)
- Lottery, 1992. (Box 34, Folder 2)
- Lottery--Administration Regulations, 1992. (Box 34, Folder 3)
- Lottery--Administration Regulations--VR 447-01-02, 1993-1994. (Box 34, Folder 4)
- Lottery--Emergency Regulations--Instant Game/On-line Game, 1991. (Box 34, Folder 5)
- Lottery--Emergency Regulations--On-line Game (Anti large block purchase) VR 477-02-2, 1992. (Box 35, Folder 1)
- Lottery--Emergency Regulations--Public Participation Guidelines, 1993. (Box 35, Folder 2)
- Lottery--Instant Game Regulations, 1992. (Box 35, Folder 3)
- Lottery--Instant Game--VR 447-02-1, 1993. (Box 35, Folder 4)
- Lottery--On-line Game Regulations--VR 447-02-2, 1992-1993. (Box 35, Folder 5)
- Lottery--On-line Game--VR 447-02-2, 1993. (Box 35, Folder 6)
- Lottery--Public Participation Guidelines, 1993. (Box 35, Folder 7)
- Marine Resources--Barrier Island Policy-VR 450-01-0058, 1990. (Box 36, Folder 1)
- Marine Resources--Public Participation Guidelines--VR 450-01-0045, 1992. (Box 36, Folder 2)
- MHMRSAS [Mental Health, Mental Retardation, and Substance Abuse]--Certification of Case Management--VR 470-05-01, 1992. (Box 36, Folder 3)
- MHMRSAS--Certification of Therapeutic Consultation and Residential Services--VR 470-05-02, 1992. (Box 36, Folder 4)
- MHMRSAS--Emergency Regulations--Certification of Case Management, 1990. (Box 36, Folder 5)
- MHMRSAS--Emergency Regulations--Certification of Case Management, Therapeutic Consultation, 1990. (Box 36, Folder 6)
- MHMRSAS--Emergency Regulations--Certification of Therapeutic Consultation and Residential Services, 1991. (Box 36, Folder 7)
- MHMRSAS--Protection of Participants in Human Research, 1992-1993. (Box 36, Folder 8)
- Mines, Minerals, and Energy--Coal Surface Mining Reclamation--VR 480-03-19, 1990-1993. (Box 36, Folder 9)
- Mines, Minerals, and Energy--Coal Surface Mining Reclamation--VR 480-03-19 (1 of 2), 1991-1993. (Box 36, Folder 10)
- Mines, Minerals, and Energy--Coal Surface Mining Reclamation--VR 480-03-19 (2 of 2), 1991-1993. (Box 36, Folder 11)
- Mines, Minerals, and Energy--Conservation of Oil and Gas Resources and Well Spacing--VR 480-05-22, 1991. (Box 36, Folder 12)
- Mines, Minerals, and Energy--Emergency Regulations--Board of Examiners Certifications Regulations--VR 480-04-2, 1993. (Box 36, Folder 13)
- Mines, Minerals, and Energy--Gas and Oil Regulation--VR 480-05-22.1 (1 of 2), 1991. (Box 37, Folder 1)
- Mines, Minerals, and Energy--Gas and Oil Regulation--VR 480-05-22.1 (2 of 2), 1991. (Box 37, Folder 2)
- Mines, Minerals, and Energy--Vertical Mine Ventilation Holes--VR 480-05-96, 1991. (Box 37, Folder 3)
- Minority Business Enterprise--Certification of Minority Business Enterprise--VR 486-01-02, 1992. (Box 37, Folder 4)
- Natural Resources--Emergency Regulations--Public Participation Guidelines, 1993. (Box 37, Folder 5)
- Personnel and Training--Public Participation Guidelines--VR 525-01-1, 1993. (Box 37, Folder 6)
- Public Safety--Emergency Regulations--Public Participation Guidelines, 1993. (Box 37, Folder 7)
- Racing Commission, 1991. (Box 37, Folder 8)
- Racing Commission--Horse Racing with Pari-Mutuel Wagering--Entries--VR 662-04-02, 1991. (Box 38, Folder 1)
- Racing Commission--Public Participation Guidelines--VR 662-01-01, 1993. (Box 38, Folder 2)
- Racing Commission--Satellite Facilities--VR 662-02-05, 1993-1994. (Box 38, Folder 3)
- Racing Commission--Virginia Breeders Fund--VR 662-04-04, 1992-1993. (Box 38, Folder 4)
- Rehabilitative Services--Emergency Regulations--Dollar Caps for Purchase of Computer Equipment and Vehicle and Home Modifications, 1992-1993. (Box 38, Folder 5)
- SAPCB [State Air Pollution Control Board]--Control and Abatement of Air Pollution-VR 120-01, 1993. (Box 38, Folder 6)
- SAPCB--Emergency Regulations-Federal Operating Permits for Stationary Sources, 1993. (Box 38, Folder 7)
- SAPCB--Emergency Regulations--Regulated Medical Waste Incinerators, 1993. (Box 38, Folder 8)
- SEAA [State Education Assistance Authority]--Edvantage Loan Program--VR 275-02-1, 1992. (Box 38, Folder 9)
- SEAA--Emergency Regulations--Virginia Guaranteed Student Loan Program and PLUS Student Loan Program, 1991. (Box 38, Folder 10)
- SEAA--Public Participation Guidelines, 1993. (Box 38, Folder 11)
- SEAA--Virginia Administration of Federally Guaranteed Student Loan Programs, Title IV, Part B, 1992. (Box 38, Folder 12)
- SEAA--Virginia Administration of Federally Guaranteed Student Loan Programs--VR 275-01-1-1, 1993. (Box 38, Folder 13)
- Social Services--Administrative Procedures for Child Development Associate Scholarship Program--VR 615-32-01, 1992. (Box 39, Folder 1)
- Social Services--Aid to Dependent Children Program--VR 615-01-029, 1992. (Box 39, Folder 2)
- Social Services--Aid to Dependent Children Program--Elimination of Monthly Reporting--VR 615-01-37, 1991-1992. (Box 39, Folder 3)
- Social Services--Aid to Families with Dependent Children--Disqualification for Intentional Program Violation--VR 615-01-49, 1992. (Box 39, Folder 4)
- Social Services--Aid to Families with Dependent Children Program--Fifth Degree Specified Relative--VR 615-01-43, 1992-1993. (Box 39, Folder 5)
- Social Services--Child Day Care--Minimum Standards for Before School and After School Care--VR 175-09-01, 1991. (Box 39, Folder 6)
- Social Services--Child Day Care--Minimum Standards for Licensed Child Care Centers, Before School, and After School Child Care Programs, 1991-1992. (Box 39, Folder 7)
- Social Services--Child Protective Services Central Registry Information--VR 615-45-1, 1991. (Box 39, Folder 8)
- Social Services--Child Protective Services--Central Registry Information--VR 615-45-1, 1991-1992. (Box 39, Folder 9)
- Social Services--Child Protective Services Client Appeals--VR 615-45-2, 1990-1992. (Box 39, Folder 10)
- Social Services--Child Protective Services Release of Information to Family Advocacy Representatives of the U.S. Armed Services--VR 615-45-3, 1993. (Box 39, Folder 11)
- Social Services--Child Support Enforcement Program--VR 615-70-17 (1 of 2), 1991-1992. (Box 39, Folder 12)
- Social Services--Child Support Enforcement Program--VR 615-70-17 (2 of 2), 1991-1992. (Box 39, Folder 13)
- Social Services--Criminal Record Checks for Child Welfare Agencies--VR 615-36-01, 1993. (Box 40, Folder 1)
- Social Services--Criminal Record Checks for Homes for Adults and Adult Day Care Centers--VR 615-37-01, 1993. (Box 40, Folder 2)
- Social Services--Disability Advocacy Project--VR 615-01-47, 1993. (Box 40, Folder 3)
- Social Services--Emergency Regulations--Adoptee Application for Disclosure of Identifying Information on Birth Family, 1992. (Box 40, Folder 4)
- Social Services--Emergency Regulations--Aid to Families with Dependent Children--Disqualification for Intentional Program Violation, 1992. (Box 40, Folder 5)
- Social Services--Emergency Regulations--Child Day Care--VR 615-53-01, 1992. (Box 40, Folder 6)
- Social Services--Emergency Regulations--Child Day Care--VR 615-53.1-01.1, 1993. (Box 40, Folder 7)
- Social Services--Emergency Regulations--Child Day Care Scholarship Program--VR 615-32-01, 1991. (Box 40, Folder 8)
- Social Services--Emergency Regulations--Child Day Care Services--VR 615-53-01, 1991. (Box 40, Folder 9)
- Social Services--Emergency Regulations--Child Support Enforcement--VR 615-70-17.14, 1992. (Box 40, Folder 10)
- Social Services--Emergency Regulations--Criminal Record Check for Homes for Adult and Adult Day Care Centers, 1992. (Box 40, Folder 11)
- Social Services--Emergency Regulations--Disability Advocacy Project--VR 615-01-47, 1992. (Box 40, Folder 12)
- Social Services--Emergency Regulations--Disability Advocacy Project--VR 615-01-47, 1993. (Box 40, Folder 13)
- Social Services--Emergency Regulations--Energy Assistance Program, 1993. (Box 40, Folder 14)
- Social Services--Emergency Regulations--Food Stamp Program Administrative Disqualification Hearings, 1991. (Box 40, Folder 15)
- Social Services--Emergency Regulations--General Relief Program--Locality Options--VR 615-01-36, 1991-1992. (Box 40, Folder 16)
- Social Services--Emergency Regulations--Voluntary Registration of Small Family Day Care Homes, 1992. (Box 40, Folder 17)
- Social Services--Emergency Regulations--Voluntary Registration of Small Family Day Care Homes--Rejected, 1991-1992. (Box 40, Folder 18)
- Social Services--Emergency Regulations--Voluntary Registration of Small Family Day Care Homes--Requirements for Contracting Organizations, 1992. (Box 40, Folder 19)
- Social Services--Fee Requirements for Processing Applications--VR 615-33-01, 1991-1992. (Box 41, Folder 1)
- Social Services--Food Stamp Program, 1992. (Box 41, Folder 2)
- Social Services--Food Stamp Program--Income Conversion Method--VR 615-01-49, 1992-1993. (Box 41, Folder 3)
- Social Services--General Procedures and Information for Licensure--VR 615-30-01, 1991-1992. (Box 41, Folder 4)
- Social Services--General Relief Program--Deeming Income from Alien Sponsors, 1993. (Box 41, Folder 5)
- Social Services--General Relief Program--Locality Options-VR 615-01-36, 1991-1993. (Box 41, Folder 6)
- Social Services--Human Subject Research-VR 615-80-01, 1993. (Box 41, Folder 7)
- Social Services--Investigation of Child Abuse and Neglect in Out of Family Complaints--VR 615-45-5, 1993. (Box 41, Folder 8)
- Social Services--Licensed Family Day Care Homes--VR 615-25-01, 1993. (Box 41, Folder 9)
- Social Services--Standards for Interdepartmental Regulations of Residential Facilities for Children (1 of 2), 1990-1991. (Box 42, Folder 1)
- Social Services--Standards for Interdepartmental Regulations of Residential Facilities for Children (2 of 2), 1990-1991. (Box 42, Folder 2)
- Social Services--Standards for Interdepartmental Regulations of Residential Facilities for Children, 1992-1993. (Box 42, Folder 3)
- Social Services--Standards for Interdepartmental Regulations of Residential Facilities for Children, 1993. (Box 42, Folder 4)
- Social Services--Standards for Licensed Homes for Adults--VR 615-22-02, 1990-1991. (Box 42, Folder 5)
- Social Services--Virginia Energy Assistance Program--VR 615-08-1, 1991. (Box 43, Folder 1)
- Social Services--Virginia Energy Assistance Program--VR 615-08-1, 1991-1992. (Box 43, Folder 2)
- Social Services--Virginia Energy Assistance Program--VR 615-08-1, 1992. (Box 43, Folder 3)